if you'd like to leave your loved ones
more than happy memories help is just a
phone call away good morning thank you
for calling sun life direct your three
to carry hiking
here at sun life direct in bristol they
specialize in life cover plans for the
over 50s they're guaranteed over 50 plan
is the most popular plan of its type in
the uk as you can hear so what is it
that keeps the phones ringing well if
you're aged 50 to 85 you're guaranteed
to be accepted without a medical that's
right guaranteed cover starts from as
little as six pounds a month and as long
as you've paid your premiums for at
least two years a catch some is paid
when you're gone so if you want to help
towards funeral costs or leave a cash
gift simply call someone direct free on
800 50 5550 and ask for an information
pack you get a free parker pen just for
inquiring the first month's premium is
free and you can choose a welcome gift
so why not call free today at 850 5550
or visit sunlife.co.uk